[{"answer": "Well, it's a gift and I want you to keep it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Wh..why didn't you tell me before you sold it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I don't need the money", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Oh, is that what this is all about?! I bounce a cheque and you sold a Cadillac?", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You're crazy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Come on, your parents have money", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "So, to what do I owe the pleasure of this, unannounced, visit", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You wanna buy it back? Why, you go drugs hidden in the trunk? my friend chuckles at his own joke. my friend stares back at him, unamused", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hey, where's my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Aw, okay.  Yeah, I need his shoeshine kit.  He always hides it from me.  Yeah, that place's? Yeah, my friend's room, please", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm worried. What happens if we have to support my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Where would you work", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Where is your resume", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Alright, my friend, I... What kind of position did you have in mind", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Do whatever you want. It's your car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It drove itself into the swamp! Besides, I think I lost my pen, too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No, no. No, no, no.  We're staying on me. We haven't solved anything yet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What d'you mean, let 'em go? They're spending all my money", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Huh? What does that do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I gotta split. my friend gets up and leaves", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "These old guys, they're up at 4 a.m., by two thirty they're wiped.  How did we get back onto you?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " You know, I got nothing outta this!  my friend, wrapped in a quilt enters the my friend's bedroom. my friend enters from the bathroom, drying his hands with a towel", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Money.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You can get that in your arms", "qsentId": 26}]